[Music]
if you're like me you probably enjoy
watching people use an ice cream scooper
on kinetic sand like would like who
doesn't love that like am i right it's
like ASMR but for your eyes one thing
I'll never understand is how do they
make kinetic sand looks so edible like
if you ate that you'd probably die that
actually dude yeah dude that looks
really good yeah like that should be
illegal how is it illegal to drive below
the speed limit but it's not illegal to
make that it literally looks like saucer
of ice cream do you think he actually
ate it I think you did what a man I
think these life hacks my tentacle week
we're not gonna be able to do any more
life hacks
the guy that guy died are you looking
for an energy boost but can't get a
regular energy drink to do the trick
anymore well just take your energy drink
and throw some double-a batteries in it
that looks like it would be really bad
for you is there gonna be a disclaimer
here
don't drink batteries all out oh that's
cool look what just exploded that would
be hilarious
do you like sleeping in public but hate
all the judgment from people around you
just take some googly eyes and stick
those suckers on your sunglasses and now
everyone will think you're wide awake
just don't try to walk around with these
on because you probably can't see a
thing
well let's have rocks
[Music]
how's a good one Thank You Surf's Up
truck just grab some rocks from outside
and cover them with fine layers a golden
spray paint for some DIY gold nugget no
joke I did this as a kid yeah that's
actually a strangely satisfying yeah it
looks good like it legit looks not that
bad but this is what companies do and
Gold's all a scam oh dude can I get a
replay of that can't get another one
okay just one more guys I'm telling you
if you're ever depressed just watch this
plate slam and I promise you it'll cheer
you up
give it to him it's a bold choice not
use fried eggs fried eggs are the
superior egg but scrambled eggs make for
a better slam yeah they do plop better
wait he thinks eggs are gross wait I
take it back if you're depressed
watch him slam a can of bacon did do you
know that is just an air freshener with
a bacon sticker really an air freshener
oh oh I thought I was like ketchup what
are we doing has God left the server you
probably love yourself some ice cream
but this is a life hack Channel so we're
gonna show you how to make your own just
take some ice cubes and put them into
your coffee mug then fill it to the brim
with some delicious pumpkin spice coffee
creamer and there you have it ice cream
oh I just got it too cuz it's ice and
cream did you just really just shut up
you didn't know it earlier she did it if
only there are more days in a year we'd
have like way more time to get stuff
done
well now you can break a hole in the
space-time continuum by literally adding
in more days to the year there's one
thing about this if you're trying to do
this you have to do it
Challenge has to be hit exactly puppy
counters no no make it stop and just
like that you've got a whole extra five
days to watch YouTube no screw this
script you sounds fine days for anime go
off the script are you tired of using
both your hands for a fork and a knife
what is what see it caveman ain't nobody
got time for that you are too white to
do that just take some hot glue and
attach a good old razor blade stuff back
of your fork it wouldn't be complete if
there was a hot glue and now you can
both cut and snap your food looking for
a way to combine your Halloween
leftovers with actual leftovers
introducing the flap jack-o'-lantern
can't say I've ever seen yellow slices
pancake thank you for being vigilant
just hold up guys let me fix my pancake
remember you got to give one pancake
enough time to dry before you do the
other pancake oh that's how you make
good earmuffs man that's what you should
do when you watch these videos it's
probably better with those pancakes over
yours yeah you can't hear our terrible
voices are you tired of having to
consistently switch between a fork and a
spoon yeah my life is terrible just slap
some of your trusty magnets because we
all have 20,000 magnets laying around to
the back of the spoon of pork and there
you go you should still some magnets
from your brother I showed out here he
has 20,000 of them so I don't think you
get this but it's a the reason it's
called a soapbox derby car because
they're made out of soap boxes okay like
the old tires on it yeah
the old ones were then they shrunk them
down in size and just made it on blocks
of wood that's a the joke here with this
guy he thinks he's funny he's taking a
box of soap and putting a car on it haha
this is the new supreme shirt man this
is how you make supreme this is how they
make supreme is this how they make a
little kid shirts I don't think so
because that doesn't look like it's
working literally at all now like evenly
dispersed glitter on the shirt
they dispersed it on this lit roller
because I doesn't roll or sticky that
looks like a popsicle yeah that's what
fish say when they eat later that's why
the glitter gets in our food and that's
why humans are slowly dying looking for
a new way to play with turbo kinetic
sand but only have red and blue
there's ruin them by mixing them
together it's not ruining them it's
making a cool color I'll be honest with
you guys we did not think this would
work so well but there you have it it's
actually works Thank You kinetics am
very sand oh he's trying to make purple
sand by mixing the other ones oh my
goodness it's a life hack if you mix
blue and pink it makes purple Wow Wow
looking to excel in school but need a
boosting confidence just snap off that
stupid safety net I'm an eraser from
your pencil and duct tape another pencil
on the other end why was that so loud it
literally sounds like they threw a
bowling ball at a wooden floor this is
for people who want to live life on the
edge and not have an eraser yeah
no going back now you better not screw
this up react to the clip where they do
two plus two is four you weren't
supposed to read that your mom wasn't
supposed to have you either but we don't
criticize her
[Applause]
this next hack is for our viewers who
suffer from chronic foot odor and have
nowhere else to go
dude he's when he brings things into
frame it always looks amazing just take
an entire bottle of heavenly hand soap
and filled those smelly Satan snakes
with enough to kill even the most
erosions bacteria egregious I don't feel
like we doing that really smelly when
you wait guys comment down below how
smelly it was it's really smelly the way
he put that down aggressively Oh gross
whoa oh gosh ah looking for an extra
edge in your tennis game take some
cardboard and fashion fins for your
balls apparently he didn't make a Harry
Potter joke about this but I think this
reminds me here thought you know I went
to Harry Potter world for my birthday
really yeah we should go there for 10
million subscribers this over oh it's
that Quidditch thing yep
oh you knew what it was I'm proud of you
I never watched it but the added
aerodynamics will make your balls faster
do you have an abundance of garbage
that's laying around your home but don't
want to suffer the scorn of your house
yes I just this script is too high IQ
for me what's their pesky high standards
to rest by giving your garbage a
makeover by adding a healthy layer of
glitter your nasty compost heap is now a
telecentric art project they'll likely
get you a grant at an institute of
higher education looking for a way to
make your school reading assignment more
interesting just read the last sentence
of the last page and spoil the ending
for yourself now that you know how
everything wraps up just skim through
the rest of the book is basketball
possible speedy just like I'm doing with
this script yeah just do that or you
could watch the movie or sparknotes
this is true sparknotes will do all your
popcorn but regardless I prefer the
inmate do you like to use coloring books
of course you do they're delightful but
do you wish there was any way to erase
those darn permanent markers if you're
accidentally colored in the long part of
the picture just take a wet sponge
squeeze some on antibiotics open show
that piece of paper who's boss within
seconds you'll see that my steak is
completely erased yeah
so no joke when we were in kindergarten
they what
give us a race if we had pencils without
erasers because you need it yeah we
needed it and I don't know what doctors
you would eat it Oh like dude that stuff
looks like DIY kinetics and ice cream
hey runs it away it's gone they have
some nice countertops they do I really
like it
oh wait is it half full yeah you got so
the glass so if he make it he's making
up a week in the turn so is it half what
happen to if he drank it then it's
half-empty if you filled it it's half
but what if he's an Australian it's
upside down hey I bought a car with
those yes you did I actually bought a
car with us no your brother bought a car
with us you're right your brother and
his handsome friend you know and Chris
was also there too oh come on why you
had to me like that well there's the
magic of everything you just not put
that in and then people would think I
was hitting on you Oh
or he could put that part in with that
other part you know what I really hate
losing my coins
so you just glue them all together yeah
that's how to do everything if I'm
scared I'm gonna lose it
I just glue it to my body like my phone
is glued to my face do you love eating
bologna sandwiches but never seem to be
able to keep the pesky thing together
oh boy do i by adding two of the world's
strongest magnets to either side of your
sandwich that little bugger won't be
going anywhere but your belly mmm
delicious I'm glad that was on the next
line so that way I can emphasize
delicious are you tired of brushing your
teeth with that dirty little toothbrush
of the week ha ha ha that toothbrush for
a whale are you being sexist I said well
that's it for the video we're about to
play rock paper scissors remember
whenever you click on a mr. Puri B's
video always watch to the end the end of
every video would play rock paper
scissors people that don't play rock
paper scissors their parents don't love
them so get your get your thing in your
hand
rock paper scissors
shoot I chose paper you chose rock take
a nail alright for this next one I
choose rock whoa wow I can't believe
you've done this
alright we're tied this one's for the
dope Rock Paper Scissors shoot
well that's super easy subscribe or your
failure
[Music]